Guide to the Robert Moog papers, circa 1965-2005.
Moog, Robert papers
- Media, 1906-2014
  - 4. Video, 1974-2005
    - DVD, 1997-2005
      - Moog in Santa Cruz, 2004; DVD-2602; Plummer, Mark (Box 72)
      - Particle Storm Digital Productions, Undated; DVD-2606; Wilhelm, David (Box 72)
      - Cavalleria Rusticana, Undated; DVD-2608; Yano, Yuki (Box 20)
      - Clara Rockmore and Lydia Kavina, 1998; DVD-2605; Asmik; Big Briar, Inc. (Box 72)
        AEBF-10099
      - Clara Rockmore and Lydia Kavina, 1998; DVD-2609; Asmik; Big Briar, Inc. (Box 20)
      - Synth Legends, 2005; DVD-2607; AudioMIDI.com (Box 72)
        Featuring Robert Moog, Tom Oberheim, Dave Smith, Roger Linn, and Marcus Ryle
      - Moog Music Theremin rough edit, Undated; DVD-2594; DIY Handmade Music (Box 16)
      - Moog Music Voyager Synthesizer - rough edit, Undated; DVD-2595; DIY Handmade Music (Box 16)
      - Sonic Infinity, 2005; DVD-2599; Moog Music, Inc. (Box 72)
      - Cape Town 2003 - Documentaries, 2004; DVD-2580; Red Bull Music Academy (Box 9)
      - Rome 2004 - Documentary, 2005; DVD-2581; Red Bull Music Academy (Box 9)
        Running time: 52 minutes, 26 seconds
      - Polar Music Prize 10th Anniversary, Undated; DVD-2674; SDC Sweden (Box 72)
      - Through the Years, Undated; DVD-2597; Video Impact (Box 72)
        Running time: 1 hour, 46 minutes
      - Gershon Kingsley's 80th Birthday Celebration, 2002; DVD-2583 (Box 9)
      - Moog Documentary, Undated; DVD-2600 (Box 72)
      - The Keyboard with Bob Moog, 2000-04-15; DVD-2601 (Box 72)
      - Theremin clips DVD-R, Undated; DVD-2379 (Box 9)
    - U-Matic, 1982-1991
      - Scatology, 1991-08-06; Bruzik, Michael; Sangsara Production Group (Box 14)
        Running time: 15 minutes
      - Letter accompanying "Scatology", 1991-09-20; Bruzik, Michael; Sangsara Production Group (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Edd Kalehoff Schaefer Beer commercial, Undated; ABC News (Box 17)
        U-Matic S tape
      - Project Termen: Clara Rockmore on Theremin, 1990-01-30; National Video Industries, Inc. (Box 14)
        "A" version - long. Running time: 9 minutes, 47 seconds
      - Camera Three Presents: The Art of the Theremin, Undated; WCBS-TV (Box 14)
      - Clara Rockmore, Theremin, Undated (Box 14)
      - Control No. 311, Undated (Box 2)
      - Groleklaug, 1982 (Box 14)
      - Project Termen: Clara Rockmore on Theremin, 1990-01-30 (Box 17)
      - Robert Moog - USIA Feature; Schaefer Beer commercial, Undated (Box 14)
      - Test #1, Test #2, 1986-06-29 (Box 14)
      - Test #3, Test #4, 1986-07-01 (Box 14)
      - Unlabeled Fuji H521E BR, Undated (Box 2)
      - Unlabeled Fuji H521E BR, Undated (Box 14)
      - Unlabeled Fuji H521E BR, Undated (Box 14)
      - Unlabeled Fuji H521E BR, Undated (Box 14)
    - Betacam, 1995-1997
      - The Visionaries, 1997-07-24; Olsen, J.P. (Box 18)
      - Clara Rockmore 3 (Japan), Undated; Big Briar, Inc. (Box 1)
      - Clara Rockmore I, Undated; Big Briar, Inc. (Box 1)
      - Clara Rockmore II, Undated; Big Briar, Inc. (Box 1)
      - Clara Rockmore master, 1998-02-10; Big Briar, Inc. (Box 1)
        Running time: 58 minutes, 30 seconds
      - Clara Rockmore: The Greatest Theremin Virtuosa, Undated; Big Briar, Inc. (Box 1)
      - Theremin Loop master, 1996-07; Big Briar, Inc. (Box 1)
        Running time: 64 minutes
      - Mastering the Theremin - Russian and English master, 1995-12-3; Little Big Films, Inc. (Box 1)
        Running time: 43 minutes, 25 seconds
      - Clara Rockmore, Undated (Box 14)
    - Other Types, 1974-2004
      - Roger Powell and Dr. Moog Newspot, interviewed by Joel Siegle, 1974; WCBS-TV (Box 18)
        EIAJ Tape
      - Clara Rockmore, No.1, Undated (Box 14)
        Sony V-12 Video Recording Tape
      - Clara Rockmore, No.2, Undated (Box 14)
      - Moog Music - Piano bar, 2004-05-10; V-10453 (Box 9)
        DV cam
      - Moog Music - Piano bar - Control voltage expander - Footage NTSC, Undated; V-10451 (Box 9)
      - Piano bar edit, 2003-10-10; V-10452 (Box 9)
  - 5. Film, Spring
    - Moog, 2003; F-1748; 16mm print (Box 21)
    - Schaeffer Beer, Undated; F-1749; 16mm print (Box 21)
      Running time: 60 seconds
    - Variable Studies, 1970; F-1750 (Box 22)
      First print from Interneg
  - 6. Software, 1982-2004
    Software arranged chronologically. Undated items arranged by name of creator.
    - Floppy Disk, 1982-2001
      - 3 1/2", 1985-2001
        - Kurzweil: Laser/Image System Disk, 1985-1987; FD-623 (Box 16)
        - Music Mouse: An Intelligent Instrument, 1987; FD-919; Spiegel, Laurie; Opcode Systems (Box 38)
          Amiga v1.00; 503.11.10423
        - Kurzweil: Bobdoc.1, 1987-03-1987-08; FD-624 (Box 16)
        - Kurzweil: Mac Write-Paint-Draw I, 1987-06; FD-621 (Box 16)
        - Kurzweil: Ensemble Grande Service Manual, 1987-10-29; FD-620 (Box 16)
        - Kurzweil: Service Manual Graphics - Ensemble Grande, 1987-10-29; FD-619 (Box 16)
        - X-OR V1.1 with MPE for Atari 520/1040/Mega ST, 1989; FD-590; Melvin, R.J. (Box 16)
          Missing disk; case only.
        - Premier Issue, 1989-04; FD-609; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - 3-D Modeling, 1989-07; FD-610; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Fractals, 1989-08; FD-611; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - DiskAnim, 1989-10; FD-612; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Expert Choices, 1989-12; FD-614; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Lintronics Advanced MemoryMoog Bankloader Manager, 1990-1991; FD-768; Branntwein, Franz; Lintronics; Musikhalle ProfiEquipment (Box 70)
        - Lintronics Advanced MemoryMoog Bankloader Manager, 1990-1991; Branntwein, Franz; Lintronics; Musikhalle ProfiEquipment (Box 70)
        - Amiga Online/Phasar 3.0, 1990-02; FD-613; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Graphics Secrets/Bars and Pipes, 1990-04; FD-615; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Summer Fun/Synthia Strings, 1990-06; FD-616; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Japanese Tiger Cub, 1990-08; FD-617; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Sounds and Spelling, 1990-10; FD-618; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - Holiday Hologram, 3-D Dog, 1990-12; FD-608; Amiga+ Magazine; Antic Publishing, Inc. (Box 16)
        - The PAN Messenger, 1991; FD-598; The PAN Network (Box 16)
        - Cubase 2.0 program disk studio copy (double sided), 1991-11; FD-588 (Box 16)
        - Keyboard I/O Double Density Gerber Files - Drilling File, 1991-12-19; FD-742 (Box 70)
        - Work at beach, 1992-08; FD-604 (Box 16)
        - PSDSoft, 1994; FD-743; WSI, Inc. (Box 70)
        - 2Q95 business disk, 1995-2000; FD-650 (Box 21)
        - BOBUBUS3Q95, 1995; FD-655 (Box 21)
        - BOBUBUS4Q95, 1995; FD-656 (Box 21)
        - Bobu's correspondence (from Senagal); also personal work for second quarter 1995., 1995; FD-652 (Box 21)
        - Dynacomp; basica.com, 1995-2000; FD-653 (Box 21)
        - Dynacomp; PC graphics, 1995-2000; FD-651 (Box 21)
        - Files from comm C drive; old theremin info files, 1995-2000; FD-649 (Box 21)
        - Bob's scratch disk, 1995-01; FD-648 (Box 21)
        - Bob's work disk, 1995-01-09-1995-03-31; FD-654 (Box 21)
        - 4Q96, 1996; FD-660 (Box 21)
        - BOBUBUS1Q96, 1996; FD-657 (Box 21)
        - BOBUBUS2Q96, 1996; FD-658 (Box 21)
        - BOBUBUS3Q96, 1996; FD-659 (Box 21)
        - From last year's NAMM show, 1996; FD-601 (Box 16)
        - Spread sheet work, 1996-03-1997-02; FD-746 (Box 70)
        - Files for Etherwave Kit Assembly Manual, 1996-03-12; FD-754 (Box 70)
          \BUILD9PL - (cover copy) \ETHWVASM - (text) \PRINTINST - (print instructions) \PANEL.PCB - (Protel) Panel wiring \Schematic - (Generic Cadd) Schematic \Silklyn - (PostScript) Component Program
        - Cheetah Win 1, 1996-05-09; FD-583 (Box 16)
        - Cheetah Win 1, 1996-05-09; FD-752 (Box 70)
          setup 1420 KB application
        - Cheetah Win 2, 1996-05-09; FD-584 (Box 16)
        - Cheetah Win 2, 1996-05-09; FD-751 (Box 70)
          setup.w02 889KB w02 File
        - Files for Hotrod manual - front office copy, 1996-07-30; FD-593 (Box 16)
        - 1Q97 BOBUBUSI1Q7, 1997; FD-761 (Box 70)
        - 97 Mail 01, Zanville, 1997; FD-602 (Box 16)
        - BOBUBUSI2H7, 1997; FD-662 (Box 21)
        - BOBUBUSI2Q7, 1997; FD-661 (Box 21)
        - Eudora "out", 1997; FD-605 (Box 16)
        - BOB.zip, 1997-03-20; FD-764 (Box 70)
          Rudi's attachment containing code for midi ther.
        - M: The Interactive Composing and Performing System, 1998; FD-917; Intelligent Computer Music Systems, Inc. (Box 38)
          Version 1.0; Serial #1207
        - BOBUBUSI1H8, 1998; FD-663 (Box 21)
        - BOBUBUSI2H8, 1998; FD-664 (Box 21)
        - M: The Interactive Composing and Performing System, 1998; FD-918 (Box 38)
          Disk 2
        - Ethervox brochure, 1998-01; FD-766 (Box 70)
          Ethervox.doc; also Clara narration
        - Wrkshp.doc, 1998-04-13; FD-765 (Box 70)
        - Minimoog and Ethervox files, 1999; FD-599 (Box 16)
        - BOBUBUSI IH9, 1999-01-1999-06; FD-665 (Box 21)
        - Cashflow.doc, 1999-02-10; FD-597 (Box 16)
        - Bob Moog personal, 1999-06-21; FD-603 (Box 16)
        - BOBUBUSI 2H9, 1999-07-1999-12; FD-666 (Box 21)
        - DBA registration diskette, 1999-08; FD-606 (Box 16)
        - Vank talk, 1999-08-05; FD-594 (Box 16)
        - BOBUBUSI 3Q00, 2000; FD-670 (Box 21)
        - BOBUBUSI 1Q00, 2000-01-2000-03; FD-667 (Box 21)
        - BOBUBUSI 2Q00, 2000-04-2000-06; FD-668 (Box 21)
        - Norton Zip Rescue Boot, 2001-10-09; FD-600 (Box 16)
        - 3d anaglyph red/blue software and 2 Mars Spirit Rover from Tim Schwartz, Undated; FD-586 (Box 16)
        - Analog board ANLG829.PCB, Undated; FD-763 (Box 70)
        - Analog PCB layout, Undated; FD-762 (Box 70)
        - Aust.txt, Undated; FD-757 (Box 70)
        - Backup of Big Briar Moneycounts files, Undated; FD-750 (Box 70)
          \MC7BUS\BACKUP89\BACKUP90
        - Bob Moog Lifetime Tour (Microsoft Word Document), Undated; FD-585 (Box 16)
        - CheetahWin2 !lydiapl.ays, Undated; FD-758 (Box 70)
        - Ethervox analog bd ANLG 326.PCB, FD-767 (Box 70)
        - Eudora "in", Undated; FD-607 (Box 16)
        - Gailrev.doc, Undated; FD-596 (Box 16)
        - It's Legal, Undated; FD-755 (Box 70)
        - keith.txt, Undated; FD-744 (Box 70)
        - Kurzweil 150 Script, Undated; FD-748 (Box 70)
        - Kurzweil: Microsoft Excel Program Disk, Undated; FD-622 (Box 16)
        - Kurzweil: Moog System, Undated; FD-625 (Box 16)
        - Kurzweil: Unlabeled, Undated; FD-626 (Box 16)
        - Kurzweil: Unlabeled, Undated; FD-627 (Box 16)
        - Kurzweil: Unlabeled, Undated; FD-628 (Box 16)
        - Kurzweil: Unlabeled, Undated; FD-629 (Box 16)
        - Kurzweil: Unlabeled, Undated; FD-630 (Box 16)
        - MIDIScope 1.1 (with system folder), Undated; FD-587 (Box 16)
        - Moneycounts Business Edition 7.5 Backup, Undated; FD-749 (Box 70)
        - Moog Manual.sit, Undated; FD-745 (Box 70)
        - Moogchad.txt, Undated; FD-760 (Box 70)
          Text of Joel Chadabe's interview
        - Opposition: 0120915 Infringement DOC1.WPD, Undated; FD-756 (Box 70)
        - Protel Autotrax Install Disk (1-61 ND) Backup, Undated; FD-759 (Box 70)
        - Protel schematic install disk (3.3/ND) backup, Undated; FD-753 (Box 70)
        - Pulver 91 (folder), Undated; FD-592 (Box 16)
        - SOS Intenies Max SimpleText, Undated; FD-591 (Box 16)
        - Tax info, talk outline, letter to fidelity, Undated; FD-595 (Box 16)
        - Unlabeled 3M disk, Undated; FD-747 (Box 70)
        - X-OR working disk #1, Undated; FD-589 (Box 16)
      - 5 1/4", 1982-1992
        - Apple BASIC: Date File Programming, 1982; FD-922; John Wiley & Sons, Inc.; Apple Computers, Inc. (Box 38)
          For Apple II; 1 disk drive; 38k minimum recommended capacity; 32k minimum capacity; 16 sector; ISBN: 0 471 86836-1
        - Golden Delicious Games for the Apple Computer, 1982; FD-920; John Wiley & Sons, Inc.; Apple Computers, Inc. (Box 38)
          For Apple II; 1 disk drive; 32k minimum recommended capacity; 16 sector; disk 1; ISBN: 0 471 86837-X
        - Golden Delicious Games for the Apple Computer, 1982; FD-921; John Wiley & Sons, Inc.; Apple Computers, Inc. (Box 38)
          For Apple II; 1 disk drive; 32k minimum recommended capacity; 16 sector; disk 2; ISBN: 0 471 86837-X
        - Track data base, 1982; FD-633 (Box 16)
        - Moogwork.1, 1984-12-331-1984-01-24; FD-635 (Box 16)
        - Amiga V1.0 Assembler Cross Development Headers, 1985; FD-738; Commodore-Amiga Inc. (Box 70)
        - Amiga V1.0 Cross-Assembler, 1985; FD-737; Commodore-Amiga Inc. (Box 70)
        - Amiga V1.0 Lattice 'C' Cross Compiler, 1985; FD-741; Commodore-Amiga Inc. (Box 70)
        - Amiga V1.0 Lattice 'C' Cross Development Headers, 1985; FD-740; Commodore-Amiga Inc. (Box 70)
        - Amiga V1.0 Lattice 'C' Cross Libraries, 1985; FD-739; Commodore-Amiga Inc. (Box 70)
        - Adventure disk #7 - first side Bill Board - Second side Latern D Gamma, 1985; FD-786 (Box 70)
        - Disk #1 Side 1: Personal Net Worth - Side 2: Modem Battle Ship, 1985; FD-788 (Box 70)
        - Disk #10 Side 1: Text files - Side 2: Text files, 1985; FD-784 (Box 70)
        - Disk #11 Side 1: Music Construction - Side 2: Axis Assasian, 1985; FD-783 (Box 70)
        - Disk #13 Side 1: Empty - Side 2: Utilities, 1985; FD-782 (Box 70)
        - Disk #14 Side 1: Zoom Graphics - Side 2: Uncommon Dictionary S.S., 1985; FD-780 (Box 70)
        - Disk #17 Side 1: Apple Writer II - Side 2: Wizplus Copy Programs, 1985; FD-779 (Box 70)
        - Disk #18 Side 1: S.C.3 - Side 2: Plus Works, 1985; FD-778 (Box 70)
        - Disk #19 Side 1: Hitch Hikers Guide to the Galaxy - Side 2: Software Speech, 1985; FD-777 (Box 70)
        - Disk #2 Side 1: Nuclear War - Side 2: Monopoly, 1985; FD-792 (Box 70)
        - Disk #20 Side 1: Home Word Main Disk - Side 2: Randam, 1985; FD-776 (Box 70)
        - Disk #22 Side 1: Pro DOS 1.0.1 1984 - Side 2: Picidally Pair, 1985; FD-775 (Box 70)
        - Disk #23 Side 1: Copy Programs - Side 2: Lost Ark, 1985; FD-774 (Box 70)
        - Disk #24 Side 1: Printer Dump (Epson) -Side 2: Joust, 1985; FD-773 (Box 70)
        - Disk #25 Side 1: Profiles - Side 2: Navigator, 1985; FD-772 (Box 70)
        - Disk #3 Side 1: Text files - Side 2: Uninitialized, 1985; FD-789 (Box 70)
        - Disk #30 Side 1: Double Talk - Side 2: Bird-Font Pack, 1985; FD-793 (Box 70)
        - Disk #31 Side 1: Apple Panic - Side 2: Heist, 1985; FD-794 (Box 70)
        - Disk #32 - First side Rescue Raiders - Second side Spy Hunter, 1985; FD-795 (Box 70)
        - Disk #33 Side 1: Pro-Dialer - Side 2: Empty, 1985; FD-771 (Box 70)
        - Disk #36 Side 1: Matt Works.1 - Side 2: Matt Works.2, 1985; FD-796 (Box 70)
        - Disk #36 Side 1: Matt Works.1 - Side 2: Matt Works.2, 1985; FD-797 (Box 70)
        - Disk #37 Side 1:MATT WORKS.3 - Side 2: MATT WORKS.4, 1985; FD-769 (Box 70)
        - Disk #37 Side 1:Matt Works.3 - Side 2: Matt Works.4, 1985; FD-798 (Box 70)
        - Disk #39 Side 1: Webster DOS 3.3 Spelling Checker - Side 2: Dictionary, 1985; FD-770 (Box 70)
        - Disk #41 Side 1: Bank Street Writer //c - Side 2: Empty, 1985; FD-799 (Box 70)
        - Disk #41 Side 1: Bank Street Writer //c - Side 2: Empty, 1985; FD-800 (Box 70)
        - Disk #42 Side 1: Bank Street Data Disk.1 - Side 2: Bank Street Data Disk.2, 1985; FD-790 (Box 70)
        - Disk #42 Side 1: Bank Street Data Disk.1 - Side 2: Bank Street Data Disk.2, 1985; FD-791 (Box 70)
        - Disk #44 Side 1: Print Shop Personal Picture Disk - Side 2: Empty, 1985; FD-801 (Box 70)
        - Disk #45 Side 1: Print Shop Graphic Capture and Viewer, 1985; FD-802 (Box 70)
        - Disk #49 Side 1: Graphics Miracles - Side 2: Empty, 1985; FD-803 (Box 70)
        - Disk #50 Side 1: Print Shop Caompanion.Backup - Side 2: Print Shop Companion.Back Up, 1985; FD-804 (Box 70)
        - Disk #51 Side 1: Print Shop.Back Up - Side 2: Dazzle Draw.Backup, 1985; FD-805 (Box 70)
        - Disk #52 Side 1: Fontrix Main Disk - Side 2: Fontpak 13, 1985; FD-806 (Box 70)
        - Disk #53 Side 1: Graphfiles - Side 2: Fontpak 1 and 2, 1985; FD-807 (Box 70)
        - Disk #54 Side 1: Fontpak 5 and 6 - Side 2: Empty, 1985; FD-808 (Box 70)
        - Disk #55 Side 1: Fontpak 7 and 8 - Side 2: Empty, 1985; FD-809 (Box 70)
        - Disk #56 Side 1: Fontpak 12 - Side 2: Empty, 1985; FD-810 (Box 70)
        - Disk #57 Side 1: Picture Disk - Side 2: Networks, 1985; FD-811 (Box 70)
        - Disk #58 Side 1: Text files - Side 2: Fontpak sampler, 1985; FD-812 (Box 70)
        - Disk #7 Side 1: Pirates Page - Side 2: Newsroom Demo, 1985; FD-787 (Box 70)
        - Disk #9 Side 1: Text files - Side 2: Text files, 1985; FD-785 (Box 70)
        - Utility disk #13 - First side Apple Term - Second side Prodos Utility Disk, 1985; FD-781 (Box 70)
        - Moogwork.2, 1985-01-09-1985-03-01; FD-636 (Box 16)
        - MIDIBoardwork.1 (Appleworks disk), 1985-03-05; FD-645 (Box 16)
        - Expanderwork.1 (Appleworks disk), 1985-03-07; FD-647 (Box 16)
        - Marketplan 85, 1985-04-04; FD-548 (Box 16)
        - Moogwork.3 (sound lib specs), 1985-04-14-1985-06-10; FD-637 (Box 16)
        - MIDIBoardwork.1 backup, 1985-04-20; FD-646 (Box 16)
        - Moogwork.4, 1985-06-10-1985-06-19; FD-638 (Box 16)
        - Moogwork.5, 1985-06-19-1985-09-10; FD-639 (Box 16)
        - Moogwork.6 - Appleworks work disk, 1985-09-10-1985-12-23; FD-641 (Box 16)
        - Moogwork.MB - MIDIBoard manual - work, 1985-12-10; FD-549 (Box 16)
        - Moogwork.7, 1985-12-30-1986-02-17; FD-642 (Box 16)
        - G W Basic 3.2 Interpreter, 1986; FD-735; Commodore Electronics Limited (Box 70)
        - MS DOS 3.2, 1986; FD-736; Commodore Electronics Limited (Box 70)
        - Apple Works Program Disk Copy #2 V1.3, 1986-02; FD-868 (Box 70)
        - Moogwork.8, 1986-02-18-1986-04-10; FD-643 (Box 16)
        - Moogwork.8.1 - first half of '86 budget, 1986-04-08-1986-06-16; FD-644 (Box 16)
        - Moogwork .9, 1986-06-18-1986-09-10; FD-873 (Box 70)
        - Moogwork .10, 1986-09-11-1986-12-01; FD-872 (Box 70)
        - Moogwork .11, 1986-12-01-1987-01-28; FD-871 (Box 70)
        - Cakewalk Release 1.1D, 1987; FD-813; Hendershott, Greg; Twelve Tone Systems (Box 70)
          Serial number: 110812-CA-1.1d
        - EasyLink Instant Mail Manager XPC Program Disk, 1987; FD-823; Kensington Microwave Ltd. (Box 70)
        - Genius Menu Maker and Menu Library, Version 7, 1987; FD-826; KYE International Corp. (Box 70)
        - Schematic Design Tools SDT III Demonstration Disk, 1987; FD-730; OrCAD Systems Corporation (Box 70)
        - Moogworks .12, 1987-01-29; FD-869 (Box 70)
        - MS DOS 3.3 ARC Utilities and Driver, 1988; FD-814; American Research Corporation (Box 70)
          Release 1.00
        - Turbo C: Command Line/Utilities, 1988; FD-818; Borland International (Box 70)
        - Turbo C: Examples/BGI/Misc, 1988; FD-815; Borland International (Box 70)
        - Turbo C: Header Files/Libraries, 1988; FD-816; Borland International (Box 70)
        - Turbo C: Install/Help, 1988; FD-819; Borland International (Box 70)
        - Turbo C: Integrated Development Environment, 1988; FD-820; Borland International (Box 70)
        - Turbo C: Libraries, 1988; FD-817; Borland International (Box 70)
        - CADD Level 2: Configuration, 1988; FD-821; Generic Software, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Program Ver 2.0 Configuration, 1988; FD-822; Generic Software, Inc. (Box 70)
          Serial No. 1LEV2-11997
        - Schema II + Demo, 1988; FD-733; Omation, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Schema II + Demo, 1988; FD-734; Omation, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Printed Circuit Board Layout Tools Demonstration Disk, 1988; FD-732; OrCAD Systems Corporation (Box 70)
        - Verification and Simulation Tools Demonstration Disk, 1988; FD-731; OrCAD Systems Corporation (Box 70)
        - EE Designer III Demo, 1988; FD-729; Visionics Corporation (Box 70)
        - All work from Derocco (1 of 2 copies), 1990-04-11; FD-847 (Box 70)
          Multi Touch Sensitive Keyboard
        - Floppy Tape - Version: 2.03 - Disk 1 of 3, 1990-10-10; FD-890; Everex, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Floppy Tape - Version: 2.03 - Disk 2 of 3, 1990-10-10; FD-891; Everex, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Floppy Tape - Version: 2.03 - Disk 3 of 3, 1990-10-10; FD-889; Everex, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Scheduler - Version: 3.02, 1990-10-10; FD-892; Everex, Inc. (Box 70)
        - All work from Derocco (1 of 2 copies), 1990-11-04; FD-850 (Box 70)
        - All work from Derocco (copy) directories: \; \source\, 1990-11-04; FD-851 (Box 70)
        - Superceded, 1990-11-04; FD-849 (Box 70)
        - Superceded, 1990-11-04; FD-852 (Box 70)
        - Superceded, 1990-11-04; FD-853 (Box 70)
        - Superceded, 1990-11-04; FD-854 (Box 70)
        - Superceded, 1990-11-04; FD-855 (Box 70)
        - The PAN Messenger - NAAM Show, 1991; FD-632; The PAN Network (Box 16)
        - System Disk MS DOS v 5.0, 1991-07; FD-887 (Box 70)
        - MIDISoft Studio for Win 3.0 - version B 0.80, 1991-09-09; FD-551; MIDISoft Corporation (Box 16)
        - The PAN Messenger, 1991-11-01; FD-631; The PAN Network (Box 16)
        - CAD Solutions CAMWare, 1992; FD-913; CAD Solutions, Inc. (Box 70)
        - Sequencer Guide Midiman, 1992; FD-878; Midiman (Box 70)
          Windows Help/Sys Ex Librarian Viewer/Channelizer
        - Bob Moog's Kscan Directory - one of two identical copies, 1992-04-27; FD-846 (Box 70)
        - Backup - KSCAN and subdirs, 1992-05-07; FD-568 (Box 16)
        - Backup - TMP and subdirs, 1992-05-07; FD-567 (Box 16)
        - Backup - Windows and subdirs - disk 1 of 4, 1992-05-07; FD-571 (Box 16)
        - Backup - Windows and subdirs - disk 2 of 4, 1992-05-07; FD-572 (Box 16)
        - Backup - Windows and subdirs - disk 3 of 4, 1992-05-07; FD-573 (Box 16)
        - Backup - Windows and subdirs - disk 4 of 4, 1992-05-07; FD-574 (Box 16)
        - Backup - Working and subdirs disk 1, 1992-05-07; FD-569 (Box 16)
        - Backup - Working and subdirs disk 2, 1992-05-07; FD-570 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 1 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-552 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 10 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-561 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 11 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-562 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 12 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-563 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 13 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-564 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 2 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-553 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 3 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-554 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 4 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-555 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 5 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-556 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 6 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-557 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 7 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-558 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 8 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-559 (Box 16)
        - Borlandc and subdirs. Backup 9 of 13, 1992-05-07; FD-560 (Box 16)
        - Copies of dirs - Belfry; old setup; editor; batch; bin; newscan; util; util/derocco (part), 1992-05-07; FD-565 (Box 16)
        - Copy - MTS, 1992-05-07; FD-566 (Box 16)
        - Copy/ DOS, 1992-05-08; FD-576 (Box 16)
        - Root dir., 1992-05-08; FD-577 (Box 16)
        - Root directory of new computer before changes, 1992-05-08; FD-575 (Box 16)
        - Uninstall 1, 1992-11; FD-888 (Box 70)
          Part of DOS 5.0 Procedure
        - \KSCAN, 1992-12; FD-848 (Box 70)
        - From M. Boyd - F1.2, 1993-06-18; FD-915; Boyd, Mark (Box 70)
        - \FP, Undated; FD-827 (Box 70)